let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which command block enables you to control the car?",
        answer: "C. When key is pressed",
        options: [
           "A. Point in direction",
            "B. Wait_secs",
            "C. When key is pressed",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the background called in Scratch ?",
        answer: "B. Stage",
        options: [
            "A. script",
            "B. Stage",
            "C.Control",
           "D. Sprite"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: " What is the function of the 'forever' command block?",
        answer: "C. Runs the script inside over and over",
        options: [
            "A. If condition is true, runs the blocks inside.",
            "B. Point sprite in specified direction",
            "C. Runs the script inside over and over",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What happens if the instruction blocks in Scratch are placed in the wrong order?",
        answer: "D.The program will not function properly because instructions are jumbled",
        options: [
            "A. The program will not work faster",
            "B. The program will not run normally",
            "C.The program will be slow",
            "D. The program will not function properly because instructions are jumbled"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What two things do all Scratch programs have ?",
        answer: "A. Scripts and sprites",
        options: [
            "A. Scripts and sprites",
            "B. Only 2 sprites",
            "C.Only stage",
            "D. Scripts and instruction"
        ]
    },
   
        {
            numb: 6,
            question: "What happens when green flag symbol is clicked?",
            answer: "C.The program starts",
            options: [
               "A.The program stops",
               "B.The program freezes",
               "C.The program starts",
               "D.The program gets deleted"
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 7,
            question: " What kind of block do I use to make my sprite move around?",
            answer: "A.Motion",
            options: [
                "A. Motion",
                "B. Control",
                "C. Sound",
                "D. Sensing "
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 8,
            question: "To execute the loop 10 times. Which command will you use ?",
            answer: "B.Repeat (10)",
            options: [
                "A.glide",
                "B.Repeat (10)",
                "C.Forever",
                "D.If ... then"
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 9,
            question: " Where do you find the broadcast option?",
            answer: "B.Control",
            options: [
                "A.Looks",
                "B.Control ",
                "C. Variable",
                "D. Motion "
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 10,
            question: "Which block is used to draw a line ?",
            answer: "A. Pen down",
            options: [
                "A. Pen down",
                "B. Show",
                "C. Motion",
                "D.Looks"
            ]
        }

    
];